[
    { "question" : "είμαι", "answer" : "to be", "pronunciation" : "/ˈime/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "έχω", "answer" : "to have", "pronunciation" : "/ˈexo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "κάνω", "answer" : "to do", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkano/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "λέω", "answer" : "to say", "pronunciation" : "/ˈleo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "πάω", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "έρχομαι", "answer" : "to come", "pronunciation" : "/ˈerxome/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "βλέπω", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvlepo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ακούω", "answer" : "to hear", "pronunciation" : "/aˈkuo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ζητάω", "answer" : "to ask", "pronunciation" : "/ziˈtao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "αγαπώ", "answer" : "to love", "pronunciation" : "/aɣaˈpo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ξέρω", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "/ˈksero/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "περιμένω", "answer" : "to wait", "pronunciation" : "/periˈmeno/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "δουλεύω", "answer" : "to work", "pronunciation" : "/ðuˈlevo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "φέρνω", "answer" : "to bring", "pronunciation" : "/ˈferno/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "βγάζω", "answer" : "to take out", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvɣazo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "καθαρίζω", "answer" : "to clean", "pronunciation" : "/kaθaˈrizo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "πρέπει", "answer" : "should", "pronunciation" : "/ˈprepi/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "κοιμάμαι", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "/ciˈmame/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "μαγειρεύω", "answer" : "to cook", "pronunciation" : "/maʝireˈvo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "θέλω", "answer" : "to want", "pronunciation" : "/ˈθelo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "κλείνω", "answer" : "to close", "pronunciation" : "/ˈklin̪o/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ανοίγω", "answer" : "to open", "pronunciation" : "/aˈniɣo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "μαθαίνω", "answer" : "to learn", "pronunciation" : "/maˈθeno/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "πληρώνω", "answer" : "to pay", "pronunciation" : "/pliˈrono/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "καταλαβαίνω", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "/katalaviˈno/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "κρατάω", "answer" : "to hold", "pronunciation" : "/kraˈtao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ανακατεύω", "answer" : "to mix", "pronunciation" : "/anakateˈvo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ρωτάω", "answer" : "to ask", "pronunciation" : "/roˈtao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "γελάω", "answer" : "to laugh", "pronunciation" : "/ʝeˈlao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "χαμογελάω", "answer" : "to smile", "pronunciation" : "/xamoʝeˈlao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "αντιλαμβάνομαι", "answer" : "to realize", "pronunciation" : "/adi̯lamaˈvome/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "χρειάζομαι", "answer" : "to need", "pronunciation" : "/çriaˈzome/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "διαβάζω", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "/ðjaˈvazo/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "ξεχνάω", "answer" : "to forget", "pronunciation" : "/kseˈçnao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "χτυπάω", "answer" : "to hit", "pronunciation" : "/çtiˈpao/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "καφές", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈfes/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "σπίτι", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/ˈspiti/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "φίλος", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "/ˈfilos/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ουράνιο τόξο", "answer" : "rainbow", "pronunciation" : "/uraˈnio ˈtoxo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "παιδί", "answer" : "child", "pronunciation" : "/peˈði/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "θάλασσα", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "/ˈθalasa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ημέρα", "answer" : "day", "pronunciation" : "/iˈmera/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "νερό", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/neˈro/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ψωμί", "answer" : "bread", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpsomi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "κρεβάτι", "answer" : "bed", "pronunciation" : "/kreˈvati/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "σχολή", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "/sxoˈli/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "εργασία", "answer" : "work", "pronunciation" : "/erɣaˈsia/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "πόλη", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpoli/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "αγορά", "answer" : "market", "pronunciation" : "/aɣoˈra/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "λουλούδι", "answer" : "flower", "pronunciation" : "/luˈluði/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "μουσική", "answer" : "music", "pronunciation" : "/musiˈki/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "καλοκαίρι", "answer" : "summer", "pronunciation" : "/kaloˈkeri/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "χρήματα", "answer" : "money", "pronunciation" : "/ˈxrimata/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "κινητό τηλέφωνο", "answer" : "mobile phone", "pronunciation" : "/ciˈnito tiˈlefono/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "πρωινό", "answer" : "breakfast", "pronunciation" : "/proi̯ˈno/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "κορίτσι", "answer" : "girl", "pronunciation" : "/koˈritsi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "μαγαζί", "answer" : "shop", "pronunciation" : "/maˈɣazi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "διακοπές", "answer" : "vacation", "pronunciation" : "/ðjaˈkopes/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "δουλειά", "answer" : "job", "pronunciation" : "/ðuˈleia/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "παραλία", "answer" : "beach", "pronunciation" : "/paraˈlia/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "μπαλκόνι", "answer" : "balcony", "pronunciation" : "/ˈbalkoni/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "σάλτσα", "answer" : "sauce", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsaltsa/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "φαγητό", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/faʝiˈto/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "αεροπλάνο", "answer" : "airplane", "pronunciation" : "/aeroˈplano/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "τραπέζι", "answer" : "table", "pronunciation" : "/traˈpezi/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "αριθμός", "answer" : "number", "pronunciation" : "/aˈriθmos/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "ταινία", "answer" : "movie", "pronunciation" : "/teˈnia/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "γραφείο", "answer" : "office", "pronunciation" : "/ɣraˈfio/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "καπέλο", "answer" : "hat", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈpelo/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "κόσμος", "answer" : "world", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkosmos/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "σκάκι", "answer" : "chess", "pronunciation" : "/ˈskaki/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "κατοικίδιο", "answer" : "pet", "pronunciation" : "/kati̯ociˈðio/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "καλός", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈlos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "κακός", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈkos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "μικρός", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/miˈkros/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "μεγάλος", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/meˈɣalos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "νέος", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/ˈneos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "παλιός", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/paˈlios/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ζεστός", "answer" : "hot", "pronunciation" : "/zeˈstos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "κρύος", "answer" : "cold", "pronunciation" : "/ˈkrios/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "όμορφος", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/ˈomorfos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "άσχημος", "answer" : "ugly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈasçimos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "δύσκολος", "answer" : "difficult", "pronunciation" : "/ˈðiskolos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "εύκολος", "answer" : "easy", "pronunciation" : "/ˈevkolos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "γρήγορος", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɣriɣoros/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "αργός", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/arˈɣos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "σημαντικός", "answer" : "important", "pronunciation" : "/simadiˈkos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "αδιάφορος", "answer" : "indifferent", "pronunciation" : "/aðiˈaforos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ήσυχος", "answer" : "quiet", "pronunciation" : "/ˈisiços/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "θορυβώδης", "answer" : "noisy", "pronunciation" : "/θoriˈvoðis/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "πρώτος", "answer" : "first", "pronunciation" : "/ˈprotos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "τελευταίος", "answer" : "last", "pronunciation" : "/telefˈteos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "καθαρός", "answer" : "clean", "pronunciation" : "/kaθaˈros/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "βρώμικος", "answer" : "dirty", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvro̞mikos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ξενύχτης", "answer" : "all-nighter", "pronunciation" : "/xeˈnixtis/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "άδειος", "answer" : "empty", "pronunciation" : "/ˈaðios/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "γεμάτος", "answer" : "full", "pronunciation" : "/ʝeˈmato̞s/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "διαφορετικός", "answer" : "different", "pronunciation" : "/ðiaforeˈtikos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ίδιος", "answer" : "same", "pronunciation" : "/ˈiðios/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ελληνικός", "answer" : "Greek", "pronunciation" : "/eliˈnikos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ξένος", "answer" : "foreign", "pronunciation" : "/ˈksenos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ανοιχτός", "answer" : "open", "pronunciation" : "/aniˈxtos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "κλειστός", "answer" : "closed", "pronunciation" : "/kliˈstos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ακριβός", "answer" : "expensive", "pronunciation" : "/akriˈvos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "φτηνός", "answer" : "cheap", "pronunciation" : "/fˈtinos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "μακρύς", "answer" : "long", "pronunciation" : "/maˈkris/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "κοντός", "answer" : "short", "pronunciation" : "/koˈntos/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "πολύ", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/poˈli/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "λίγο", "answer" : "a little", "pronunciation" : "/ˈliɣo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "πάντα", "answer" : "always", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpanda/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "συχνά", "answer" : "often", "pronunciation" : "/sihˈna/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ποτέ", "answer" : "never", "pronunciation" : "/poˈte/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "πουθενά", "answer" : "nowhere", "pronunciation" : "/puˈθena/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "παντού", "answer" : "everywhere", "pronunciation" : "/panˈtu/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "εδώ", "answer" : "here", "pronunciation" : "/eˈðo/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "εκεί", "answer" : "there", "pronunciation" : "/eˈci/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "μακριά", "answer" : "far", "pronunciation" : "/maˈcria/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "κοντά", "answer" : "near", "pronunciation" : "/koˈnda/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ήδη", "answer" : "already", "pronunciation" : "/ˈidi/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "μόλις", "answer" : "just", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmolis/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ακόμα", "answer" : "still", "pronunciation" : "/aˈkoma/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ίσως", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/ˈisos/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "βέβαια", "answer" : "certainly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈvevea/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "σίγουρα", "answer" : "surely", "pronunciation" : "/ˈsiɣura/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "γρήγορα", "answer" : "quickly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈɣriɣora/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "αργά", "answer" : "slowly", "pronunciation" : "/arˈɣa/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ολόκληρα", "answer" : "entirely", "pronunciation" : "/oˈloclira/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "μόνο", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmono/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "πάλι", "answer" : "again", "pronunciation" : "/ˈpali/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "προηγουμένως", "answer" : "previously", "pronunciation" : "/proiɣuˈmenos/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "έτσι", "answer" : "like this", "pronunciation" : "/ˈetsi/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "αλλιώς", "answer" : "differently", "pronunciation" : "/aˈlios/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "καλύτερα", "answer" : "better", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈlitera/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "χειρότερα", "answer" : "worse", "pronunciation" : "/çiˈrotera/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "επίσης", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/eˈpisis/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "μόνιμα", "answer" : "permanently", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmonima/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "προσεχτικά", "answer" : "carefully", "pronunciation" : "/proseçˈtika/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "απλά", "answer" : "simply", "pronunciation" : "/aˈpla/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "θερμά", "answer" : "warmly", "pronunciation" : "/ˈθerma/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "κρυφά", "answer" : "secretly", "pronunciation" : "/kriˈfa/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "δημοσίως", "answer" : "publicly", "pronunciation" : "/ðimoˈsios/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ιδιαιτέρως", "answer" : "particularly", "pronunciation" : "/iðieˈteros/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "ανοιχτά", "answer" : "openly", "pronunciation" : "/aˈnihta/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "σκληρά", "answer" : "hard", "pronunciation" : "/skliˈra/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "και", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/ke/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "αλλά", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/aˈla/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "όμως", "answer" : "however", "pronunciation" : "/ˈomos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "επειδή", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/epiˈði/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "εάν", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/eˈan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "όταν", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/ˈotan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "πριν", "answer" : "before", "pronunciation" : "/prin/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "μετά", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/meˈta/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ενώ", "answer" : "while", "pronunciation" : "/eˈno/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "επίσης", "answer" : "also", "pronunciation" : "/eˈpisis/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "οπότε", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/oˈpote/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "αφού", "answer" : "after", "pronunciation" : "/aˈfu/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "διότι", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/ðiˈoti/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ίσως", "answer" : "maybe", "pronunciation" : "/ˈisos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "έτσι", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/ˈetsi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "έπειτα", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/ˈepita/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "μέχρι", "answer" : "until", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmexri/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ούτως", "answer" : "thus", "pronunciation" : "/ˈutos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "έντωμεταξύ", "answer" : "meanwhile", "pronunciation" : "/endomeˈtaxi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ουσιαστικά", "answer" : "basically", "pronunciation" : "/usiastiˈka/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "εξάλλου", "answer" : "moreover", "pronunciation" : "/eˈksalu/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "αντίθετα", "answer" : "instead", "pronunciation" : "/anˈtiθeta/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "επομένως", "answer" : "consequently", "pronunciation" : "/epoˈmenos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "από", "answer" : "from", "pronunciation" : "/aˈpo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "καθώς", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/kaˈðos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ακόμα", "answer" : "even", "pronunciation" : "/aˈkoma/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ειδάλλως", "answer" : "otherwise", "pronunciation" : "/iˈðalos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "συνεπώς", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/sineˈpos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "σαφώς", "answer" : "clearly", "pronunciation" : "/saˈfos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "πώς", "answer" : "how", "pronunciation" : "/pos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "τουλάχιστον", "answer" : "at least", "pronunciation" : "/tuˈlaxiston/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "παρόλο", "answer" : "although", "pronunciation" : "/paˈrolo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "απόψε", "answer" : "tonight", "pronunciation" : "/aˈpopse/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "μόνο", "answer" : "only", "pronunciation" : "/ˈmono/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "οπόταν", "answer" : "whenever", "pronunciation" : "/oˈpotan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "οπωσδήποτε", "answer" : "anyhow", "pronunciation" : "/oposðiˈpote/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "αντιθέτως", "answer" : "on the contrary", "pronunciation" : "/andiˈθetos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ούτε", "answer" : "nor", "pronunciation" : "/ˈute/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "συγχρόνως", "answer" : "at the same time", "pronunciation" : "/siŋˈhronos/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]